integrativenutrition.com 2008-06-21

# integrativenutrition.com | Terms of Use

**INTEGRATIVE NUTRITION PRIVACY POLICY**

This statement discloses the privacy practices for the Integrative Nutrition family of web sites (www.integrativenutrition.com) hereafter referenced as Integrative Nutrition, or "us" or "we." 

PLEASE REVIEW THIS POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.   
By using any Integrative Nutrition website, you agree to the terms of these policies. If you do not agree to such terms, you may not use and must exit this web site. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**

We strive to provide information and services that are tailored to our users' needs. To do this, we may ask that you provide personal information when you do any of the following: request a catalog/magazine, order books, take our quiz, subscribe to newsletters, or request customer service. We only collect personally identifiable information that you submit voluntarily. If you choose not to provide personally identifiable information, you can still use the website, but will not be able to use the services that require such information. 

**WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION**

Integrative Nutrition collects personal information only with the express consent of the user when they request information from the Integrative Nutrition Network. This information is only used when communicating with users as per their indicated preferences and as needed for service-related communications. 

In the event of an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of some or all of the assets of Integrative Nutrition, Inc., you agree that we can accordingly assign, sell, license or transfer any information that our Users have provided to us. Please note, however, that the purchasing party can not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent. 

Integrative Nutrition may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to others or interfering with Integrative Nutrition's rights or property. 

**OPTING OUT**

Integrative Nutrition provides users with the ability to opt out for communications from any of the Integrative Nutrition newsletters. 

**SECURITY OF INFORMATION**

The security of our users' personally identifiable information is of the highest priority. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through our Services, and you do so at your own risk. 

Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Whenever credit card information is transmitted, we use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Only those who have your username and password can access your account information. We strongly recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please remember to sign out properly and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This helps ensure that others cannot access your personal information. 

**POLICY MODIFICATIONS**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Be assured that even if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [tech@integrativenutrition.com](mailto:tech@integrativenutrition.com).
